Guide to the Nicole Di Bona Peterson Collection of Advertising Cookbooks, 1850s-2000s
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University, Durham, N.C., USA
- American Cookbooks 1960s, 11
  - Here's How to Make Danish Pastry with Allsweet, 1960 (Box C14, Item 1960sC-0051)
    Note: black-and-white photographs, by Martha Logan
  - Automatic Grill and Waffle Baker, circa 1960s (Box C14, Item 1960sC-0052)
    Product: Grill and Waffle Baker
  - Deluxe Automatic Mixmaster Mixer…Instruction and Recipe Book, 1968 (Box C14, Item 1960sC-0053)
    Product: Mixer
    Note: black-and-white photographs of Sunbeam appliances on back, tan color highlights inside
  - Deluxe Osterizer Recipes, 1963 (Box C14, Item 1960sC-0054)
    Product: Deluxe Osterizer
    Note: color illustrated
  - Hamilton Beach…Where New Ideas Help You Live Relaxed!, circa 1960s (Box C14, Item 1960sC-0055)
  - Mirro-Matic Speed Pressure Cooker and Canner, circa 1960s (Box C14, Item 1960sC-0056)
    Product: deluxe model Speed Pressure Cooker and Canner
  - Multi-Cooker Frypan (Buffet Style) with Removable Heat Control, circa 1960s (Box C14, Item 1960sC-0057)
    Product: Sunbeam Vista Multi-Cooker Frypan
    Note: tells how to mail appliance to service station, where factory parts come from
  - Calorie Saving Recipes with Sucaryl Sweeteners…Non-Caloric Sweeteners for Reducing and Diabetic Diets, 1967 (Box C14, Item 1960sC-0058)
    Product: Sucaryl tablets
  - Duke Power Electric Recipes, circa 1960s (Box C14, Item 1960sC-0059)
  - Holiday Recipes, circa 1960s (Box C14, Item 1960sC-0060)
  - 11 year-round favorite Sliced Baby Tomato recipes from...Contadina, circa 1960s (Box C14, Item 1960sC-0061)
    Company: Contadina
    Product: Contadina sliced baby tomatoes
  - care and serving of Avocados, circa 1960s (Box C14, Item 1960sC-0062)
    Company: King Salad
    Product: King Salad Avocados
  - Nancy Wards' Quick-Fix Potato Recipe Book, 1968 (Box C14, Item 1960sC-0063)
    Company: San Luis Valley Potato Administrative Committee
    Product: Potato
    Note: cartoon of Spanish conquistador, black-and-white illustrations, color photographs of valley
  - Borden's Eagle Brand magic Recipes, 1964 (Box C14, Item 1960sC-0064)
    Product: Eagle Brand Sweetened Condensed Milk, Borden's Instant Coffee
  - The Gourmet's Guide to Dining and Drinking 8th edition, 1963 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0001)
  - Fleischmann's Mixer's Manual, circa 1960s (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0002)
  - Miss Annie's Recipes, circa 1960s (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0003)
    Company: George A. Dickel General Merchandise Store
    Product: George Dickel whiskey
  - Deep South Cookery and Potables, 1968 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0004)
    Product: Rebel Yell bourbon
  - Strawberry Chiffon Cake, circa 1960s (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0005)
  - Yeast Breads, 1968 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0006)
  - Let's Bake The Robin Hood No-Sift Way, 1964 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0007)
  - A New Way to Bake!, circa 1960s (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0008)
  - Famous Chocolate Frostings Made Easy, 1967 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0009)
  - Recipes with Ketchup, 1966 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0010)
    Product: Del Monte ketchup
  - Gourmet Conveniences, 1960 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0011)
  - Tune Up Your Spring and Summer Cooking, 1960 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0012)
  - 100 Ways to Be Original in All Your Cooking, 1964 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0013)
    Product: Lea & Perrins Worcestershire sauce
  - Exciting New Recipes, 1964 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0014)
    Product: Duranel cookware
  - Adventures in Chafing Dish Cookery, 1961 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0015)
    Company: Globe-Ware Industries
    Product: Globe-Ware chafing dishes
  - Favorite Recipes, circa 1960s (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0016)
    Product: Nordic-Ware cookware
  - Your Guide to Creative Cooking, 1966 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0017)
    Product: Aristo Craft cookware
  - Kid-Pleasin' Meals Menus and Recipes, 1967 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0018)
  - Merrymeals with Kid Appeal, 1963 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0019)
  - Cooking with a Surprising Difference, 1966 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0020)
    Note: Water damage
  - Dessert Spectaculars!, 1960 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0021)
  - Start Cooking with a Golden Spoon, 1960 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0022)
  - Toast of the Town, 1967 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0023)
    Product: Sealtest egg nog
  - Famous Florida Chefs' Favorite Citrus Recipes, 1966 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0024)
  - Southern Grape Recipes, circa 1960s (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0025)
    Company: Ison's Vineyard
    Product: Grapes
  - Joys of Jell-O, 1963 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0026)
  - Magical Desserts with Whip'n Chill, 1965 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0027)
    Product: Whip'n Chill
  - Prize Winning Gel-Cookery Recipes, 1961 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0028)
  - Untitled, circa 1960s (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0029)
  - Party Sandwich Ideas with Wonder Bread, circa 1960s (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0030)
    Company: Interstate Bakeries Corporation
  - Menu Magic, 1969 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0031)
    Product: Kellogg's Croutettes
  - Our Favorites for Family and Friends, 1967 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0032)
  - Round the Clock Recipes, 1963 (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0033)
    Note: Mary Alden
  - Miss Fluffy's Rice Cook Book, circa 1960s (Box D24, Item 1960sD-0034)
  - Metropolitan Cook Book, 1964 (Box D25, Item 1960sD-0035)
  - Bar-B-Bowl Recipes, circa 1960s (Box D25, Item 1960sD-0036)
    Company: Bar-B-Bowl
    Product: Bar-B-Bowl barbecue grills
    Note: Recipes from Good Housekeeping magazine
  - Getting the Most from Your GE Range, 1961 (Box D25, Item 1960sD-0037)
  - A Dozen Ways to Stretch Your Beef Dollar, circa 1960s (Box D25, Item 1960sD-0038)
    Company: Beef Industry Council
  - Seafood Moods, 1969 (Box D25, Item 1960sD-0039)
    Company: U. S. Department of the Interior
    Product: Pacific seafood
  - How to Prepare Exciting Holiday Menus, 1964 (Box D25, Item 1960sD-0040)
    Company: Amy Vanderbilt Success Program for Women
    Note: Charlotte Adams
  - 31 Take It Easy Recipes, 1961 (Box D25, Item 1960sD-0041)
    Product: Grocery chain
    Note: Nancy Carter
  - Famous Kitchens The Brand Names Cook Book, 1961 (Box D25, Item 1960sD-0042)
    Note: Marguerite English, damaged with back cover missing
  - Food Flavor, Facts and Fun for Folks After Fifty, 1965 (Box D25, Item 1960sD-0043)
    Company: Durham Golden Age Society (Durham, N.C.)
  - Pennsylvania Dutch Cookie Recipes, 1964 (Box D25, Item 1960sD-0044)
    Company: Dutchcraft Company
  - Anniversary Cook Book, 1968 (Box D25, Item 1960sD-0045)
    Company: North Carolina Academy of General Practice
  - Deck the Halls…, circa 1960s (Box D25, Item 1960sD-0046)
    Company: Person County (N.C.) Public School System
  - Fondue for Fun, 1969 (Box D25, Item 1960sD-0047)
    Company: Roberts Colonial House, Inc.
  - Fryingpan's West, 1969 (Box D25, Item 1960sD-0048)
    Company: Sam Arnold
    Note: KRMA-TV (Denver, Colo.) television program
  - Better Breakfast for Better Health, 1966 (Box D25, Item 1960sD-0049)
    Note: General Motors employee information rack item
  - Green Vegetables for Good Eating, 1961 (Box D25, Item 1960sD-0050)
    Note: Home and Garden Bulletin No. 41
  - Home Canning of Fruits and Vegetables, 1967 (Box D25, Item 1960sD-0051)
    Note: Home and Garden Bulletin No. 8
  - Keeping Food Safe to Eat, 1969 (Box D25, Item 1960sD-0052)
    Note: Home and Garden Bulletin No. 162
  - Root Vegetables in Everyday Meals, 1961 (Box D25, Item 1960sD-0053)
    Note: Home and Garden Bulletin No. 33
  - Tips on Selecting Fruits and Vegetables, 1961 (Box D25, Item 1960sD-0054)
    Note: Marketing Bulletin No. 13
  - Good Eating to You, circa 1960s (Box D25, Item 1960sD-0055)
    Company: WNAD Radio, University of Oklahoma
    Note: Chef Thomas L. Farrell
  - Ocracoke Cook Book, 1964 (Box D26, Item 1960sD-0056)
    Company: Women's Society of Christian Service, United Methodist Church (Ocracoke, N.C.)
  - Pennsylvania Dutch Pie Recipes, circa 1960s (Box D26, Item 1960sD-0057)
    Company: Yorkraft
  - All-American Favorite Recipes, 1960 (Box D26, Item 1960sD-0058)
  - A Treasury of the World's Best Almond Recipes, 1963 (Box D26, Item 1960sD-0059)
  - Celebration Recipes, 1969 (Box D26, Item 1960sD-0060)
  - Golden Good Cooking, 1963 (Box D26, Item 1960sD-0061)
    Product: Saff-O-Lite safflower oil
  - Formulas for Bakers, circa 1960s (Box D26, Item 1960sD-0062)
    Product: Wesson oils and shortening
  - What's For Lunch Cook Book, 1968 (Box D26, Item 1960sD-0063)
  - Use and Care Book with Recipes, circa 1960s (Box D26, Item 1960sD-0064)
    Product: GE buffet skillet
  - Spin Cookery, 1969 (Box D26, Item 1960sD-0065)
  - Instructions and Recipes, 1966 (Box D26, Item 1960sD-0066)
    Product: Ronson 5-speed blender
  - Complete Blender Cook Book, 1965 (Box D26, Item 1960sD-0067)
  - College Inn Comes to Dinner, circa 1960s (Box D26, Item 1960sD-0068)
    Company: RJR Foods, Inc.
    Product: College Inn chicken and beef broth
  - Favorite Recipes, circa 1960s (Box D26, Item 1960sD-0069)
  - Miscellaneous recipes, circa 1960s (Box D26, Item 1960sD-0070)
    Product: Pure maple syrup
  - Holiday Fare, circa 1960s (Box D26, Item 1960sD-0071)
  - Merry Christmas, circa 1960s (Box D26, Item 1960sD-0072)
  - Recipes, 1965 (Box D26, Item 1960sD-0073)
  - Recipes for Electric Holiday Living, 1963 (Box D26, Item 1960sD-0074)
  - Waist Watchers, circa 1960s (Box D26, Item 1960sD-0075)
    Company: Florida Celery Advisory Committee
    Product: Florida celery
  - New Ideas for Royal Viking Danish Mix, circa 1960s (Box D40, Item 1960sD-OV01)
    Product: Royal Viking Danish pastry mix
  - Simplified Cake Decorating, 1960 (Box D40, Item 1960sD-OV02)
    Company: August Thomsen Corporation
    Product: Ateco cake decorating equipment
  - Danish Food in America, circa 1960s (Box D40, Item 1960sD-OV03)
    Company: Denmark in the U.S.A. Committee
    Product: Danish food
  - Cakes, Buns and Biscuits, 1961 (Box D40, Item 1960sD-OV04)
  - Sexton Food Serving Chart, 1960 (Box D40, Item 1960sD-OV05)
    Product: Sexton canned foods
  - For Profit Cook with Soup, 1960 (Box D40, Item 1960sD-OV06)
  - Festive Foods, 1967 (Box D40, Item 1960sD-OV07)
    Company: Wisconsin Gas Company
  - Daisy Fresh Corporation 'Best in the Land' 1965 Drink More Calendar, 1965 (Box OV 01, Item OZ 1960s-0002)
    Company: Dairy Fresh Corporation
    Product: Milk, ice cream
    Note: graphic & photographic illustrations with children. Boy and girl eating and drinking milk, playing leapfrog, etc. Inside, health and other benefits of milk
  - Art of Salad Making, circa 1960s (Box OV 01, Item OZ 1960s-0003)
    Product: Libby canned fruits
  - Knox On-Camera Recipes: A Completely New Guide to Gel-Cookery, 1962 (Box OV 01, Item OZ 1960s-0004)
    Note: color & black-and-white illustrations, Cover is mock-up of cooking show, woman in kitchen (set) while man works camera in foreground. Intended to make recipes easier to follow. Weight: gelatin as diet food.
  - Freezer Living is Good Living with Coldspot, 1964 (Box OV 01, Item OZ 1960s-0005)
    Note: spokesperson Jean Shaw. Modern art cover, inside illustrations of woman in kitchen. Economy and convenience of freezers
  - Fuller Brush Calendar Magazine, 1963 (Box OV 01, Item OZ 1960s-0006)
    Company: Fuller Brush Company
    Product: Fuller Brush toiletry items
    Note: Cover illustration of mother and daughter cooking, inside pictures of various family, teen, and social settings.
  - New Ford Treasury of Favorite Recipes from Famous Restaurants, 1963 (Box OV 01, Item OZ 1960s-0007)
    Product: Ford Motor Company
    Note: color drawings of various restaurants, drive-ins, hotels, etc. US regional specialties.
  - 5 Great Cuisines with Planter's Peanut Oil, 1967 (Box OV 01, Item OZ 1960s-0008)
    Product: Planter's Peanut Oil, etc.
    Note: color illustrations including a layout of all Standard Brands products. International.
  - Chocolate and Coconut Treats, 1962 (Box OV 01, Item OZ 1960s-0009)
    Product: Baker's Chocolate, Baker's Coconut, Calumet Baking Powder
    Note: color illustrations including family life and entertaining. 'Any girl old enough to have a boyfriend knows that the prospect of chocolate chip cookies, chocolate cake, and chocolate brownies will bring the men a-running.' For adult women and teenaged girls, 'hostesses'
  - Fleischmann's New Treasury of Yeast Baking, 1967 (Box OV 01, Item OZ 1960s-0010)
    Product: Fleischmann's Dry Yeast, Fleischmann's Margarine, Planter's Peanut Oil, etc.
    Note: color illustrations including a layout of all Standard Brands products. History of yeast and yeast-baking
  - Food for You and Your Family, 1968 (Box OV 01, Item OZ 1960s-0011)
    Product: Baker's Chocolate, Jell-O, Minute Rice, Good Seasons salad dressings, etc.
  - 2 Handy 'Make-Your-Own' Mixes with Swift Shortening, 1965 (Box OV 01, Item OZ 1960s-0012)
    Note: spokesperson Martha Logan
  - Teen Time in the Kitchen, circa 1960s (Box OV 01, Item OZ 1960s-0013)
    Company: Potomac Edison, Allegheny Power System
    Note: Aimed at teens, with intent to prepare them for managing their own kitchen in the future
  - Basic Yeast Bread, 1966 (Box OV B02, Item OZ 1960sB-0001)
    Product: Robin Hood Flour and Fleischmann's Yeast
    Note: black-and-white demonstration photographs, preparation instructions
  - Pillsbury's Bake Off Dessert Cook Book, 1968 (Box OV B02, Item OZ 1960sB-0002)
    Product: Pillsbury products (All-purpose flour)
    Note: Color photographs, basics, terms, measures, hints
  - Well-Dressed Dessert, 1969 (Box OV B02, Item OZ 1960sB-0003)
    Product: Multiple products incl. Cool Whip
    Note: Color photographs and drawings, flip-page cookbook (part two on reverse of part one), can stand on its own
  - In the Best Taste, Flair Without Fuss with Shake'n Bake, 1969 (Box OV B02, Item OZ 1960sB-0004)
    Product: Shake 'n Bake
    Note: Color photographs, descriptions at beginning of each section
  - Sunkist Cook Book, 1968 (Box OV B02, Item OZ 1960sB-0005)
    Note: Spiral bound, color photographs and drawings, kitchen secrets
  - How to Prepare Foods for Freezing, 1962 (Box OV B02, Item OZ 1960sB-0006)
    Note: black-and-white photographs, drawings, and diagrams, Q&A about freezing, thawing time tables
  - How to Prepare Foods for Freezing, 1961 (Box OV B02, Item OZ 1960sB-0007)
    Note: Same as OZ1960sB-0006
  - Your Kenmore Time Bank Freezer for the Time of Your Life, circa 1960s (Box OV B02, Item OZ 1960sB-0008)
    Product: Kenmore Time Bank Freezer
    Note: black-and-white photographs, black-and-white and orange drawings, tips, preparation tables
  - Modern Sandwich Methods, 1964 (Box OV B02, Item OZ 1960sB-0009)
    Product: Sandwiches
    Note: black-and-white (and orange) drawings, designed for people dealing with mass production of sandwiches, pointers and tips
  - Food For You and Your Family, 1967 (Box OV B02, Item OZ 1960sB-0010)
    Note: Color photographs and drawings, Be and Artist at Breakfast inserted inside, Kitchen tips, Nutritional food chart for General Foods products
  - Betty Crocker's Cooky Book, 1963 (Box OV C02, Item OZ 1960sC-0001)
    Note: spiral bound, color and black-and-white illustrations
  - Fleischmann's New Treasury of Yeast Baking, 1968 (Box OV C02, Item OZ 1960sC-0002)
    Product: Fleischmann's Active Dry Yeast, Margarine, Chase & Sanborn Coffee
  - McCormick's Spices of the World Cookbook, 1964 (Box OV C02, Item OZ 1960sC-0003)
    Product: McCormick spices
    Note: ring binder, tabbed sections, color photographs
  - Our Daily Bread, circa 1960s (Box OV C02, Item OZ 1960sC-0004)
  - Home Canning and Freezing Sketch Book, 1961 (Box OV C02, Item OZ 1960sC-0005)
  - Tru-Cold Refrigerator Owner's Guide, circa 1960s (Box OV C02, Item OZ 1960sC-0006)
    Product: Tru-Cold Appliances
  - Recipes and Menus for All Seasons, circa 1963 (Box OV C02, Item OZ 1960sC-0007)
    Product: Sexton foods (institutional food service)
    Note: cost-per-serving charts, recipes for large service
  - Treasury of Good Food Ideas from the Kraft Kitchens, 1963 (Box OV C02, Item OZ 1960sC-0008)
    Product: Kraft cheese, sauces, jelly, crackers
    Note: ring binder
  - The Choicest Vegetables… A Fleischmann's Corn-Oil Margarine Pin-Up, circa 1960s (Box OV C02, Item OZ 1960sC-0009)
    Product: Fleischmann's Corn-Oil Margarine
  - A Campbell Cookbook… Easy Ways to Delicious Meals, 1969 (Box OV C02, Item OZ 1960sC-0010)
    Product: Various Campbell Soup products
    Note: Very large bold print recipes, 2 photographs
  - Stokely Portfolio of Garden Favorites, circa 1960s (Box OV C02, Item OZ 1960sC-0011)
    Product: Stokely tomatoes, catsup, sliced peaches, green beans, golden corn, fruit cocktail
    Note: large dimensions, illustrated by Guy Coheleach, color photographs
- American Cookbooks 1970s, 12
  - ... And Add a Measure of Gold, circa 1970s (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0001)
    Company: Distillerie Riunite di Liquori
    Product: Liquore Galliano
  - The BACARDI Party Book, 1972 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0002)
    Product: Bacardi Rum
  - Calvert Party Encyclopedia, circa 1970s (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0003)
    Product: Calvert liquors
  - Cointreau Secrets of Flaming Desserts, circa 1970s (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0004)
    Note: Spokespeople: Pierre, Robert, and Max Cointreau
  - Cooking With Wine, 1976 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0005)
    Company: Holland House Brand Inc.
    Product: Holland House Cooking Wine
    Note: in original envelope, featuring John J. Poister and associated with Woman's Day Magazine
  - Discover Gold, circa 1970s (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0006)
    Note: Illustration of man wearing apron and mixing drinks
  - Fleischmann's Mixer Manual, 1975 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0007)
    Product: Fleischmann's Preferred alcohols (whiskey, gin, vodka, bourbon, & scotch)
  - Four Roses Guide to Happy Hostmanship, circa 1970s (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0008)
    Company: Four Roses Distillers Company
    Product: Four Roses (American light whiskey)
    Note: Cover illustration of male leaning over woman in low-cut dress
  - Hapa Hawaiian Pupu and Cocktails, 1970s (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0009)
    Product: cocktails, hors d'oeuvres
    Note: recipe contributors are employees of Hawaiian business, (hotels, restaurants, etc.)
  - Happy Hour Barguide: 45 Great Drink Recipes, 1970 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0010)
    Note: Illustrations of couples of young men and women
  - Happy Hour Mixology, 1973 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0011)
  - History of Mixed Drinks and how to mix 42 great ones, circa 1970s (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0012)
  - How to Cook with California Wines, circa 1970s (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0013)
  - Legendary Liqueur, 1979 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0014)
    Product: Irish Mist
    Note: Appeals to Irish history
  - Manjo Mirin Japanese Sweet Sake for cooking and cocktails, circa 1970s (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0015)
    Company: Manjo Mirin
    Product: Japanese Sweet Sake
  - Menus for Every Mood, circa 1970s (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0016)
  - New! White Yago Sant'gria, 1971 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0017)
    Company: Monsieur Henri Wines, Ltd.
    Product: Yago White Sant'gria
  - Pour and Easy Rum Party, 1974 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0018)
    Company: Rums of Puerto Rico
    Product: Puerto Rican rum
    Note: Puerto Rican product, published in US
  - Recipe Favorites from Early Times, circa 1970s (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0019)
    Company: Early Times
    Product: Early Times Kentucky Bourbon
  - Recipes the whole family will enjoy, circa 1970s (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0020)
    Note: Mogen David wine 'like Grandma used to make'
  - Spirit of '76 Happy Hour Barguide, 1976 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0021)
  - Untitled, 1971 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0022)
    Company: McKesson Liquor Company, Distillerie Riunite di Liquori
    Product: Liquore Galliano 80 Proof
  - Year of the Brunch, circa 1970s (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0023)
    Company: Smirnoff
  - Your Amaretto di Saronno Gourmet Secrets, 1974 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0024)
    Company: Foreign Vintages, Inc.
    Product: Amaretto di Saronno
    Note: provides some mythical Italian history. 'Love at first sip.'
  - 9 Creative puff pastry Recipes, circa 1970s (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0025)
    Product: frozen patty shells
    Note: associated with Ladies' Home Journal
  - 250 Superb Pies and Pastries, 1974 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0026)
    Product: Ceresota and Heckers unbleached flour
    Note: spokesperson Helen Hiland
  - Betty Crocker's Bisquick Cookbook Chapter One – Holiday Hospitality, 1971 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0027)
    Product: Bisquick Baking Mix
  - Bisquick Holiday Bakeshop, 1977 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0028)
  - Cakes Kids Love, 1976 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0029)
    Product: Betty Crocker Frosting
    Note: Recipes for children
  - Easy as Pie Festive Recipes for Betty Crocker Pie Crust and Mix, 1972 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0030)
    Product: Betty Crocker Pie Crust Sticks and Mix
    Note: Spokesperson: Betty Crocker. Holiday theme
  - Festive Baking for All Seasons, 1976 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0031)
  - Folk Breads, USA: Betty Crocker's Bisquick Cookbook, Supplement Three, 1973 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0032)
    Note: Patriotism: distinctly 'American' foods. Includes short origins, traditions associated with each recipe
  - Holiday Buffets: Menus and Recipes for Very Special Occasions, circa 1970s (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0033)
    Company: Martha White Foods
    Product: Spudflakes, Martha White cornmeal and flour
    Note: Holiday theme, cartoon illustrations
  - How To' Decorating Basics from cake mate, 1978 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0034)
    Product: Cake Mate
    Note: caters to children and mothers
  - The Morning Show, 1974 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0035)
  - My Favorite Christmas Recipes, circa 1970s (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0036)
    Product: Martha White Flour, Martha White Self-Rising Corn Meal, etc.
    Note: Spokesperson: Tennessee Ernie Ford, celebrity. Theme of book is Ford's traditional family holiday meals.
  - New Way to Bake! With Pillsbury Instant Blending Flour, circa 1970s (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0037)
    Product: Pillsbury Instant Blending Flour
    Note: Spokesperson: Ann Pillsbury.
  - Nice 'n Easy Cook Book, circa 1970s (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0038)
    Product: Pillsbury's Refrigerated Foods
    Note: Spokesperson: Ann Pillsbury. Includes menus for 'Busy Lady Luncheon' and 'A Dinner for a Special Man.'
  - Solo Cake and Pastry Fillings Cookbook, circa 1970s (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0039)
    Company: Sokol & Company
    Product: Solo Cake and Pastry Fillings
  - Spice Island Cook's Survival Cookbook, 1978 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0040)
    Company: Specialty Brands Inc.
  - Strictly Thrifty Menus: Betty Crocker's Bisquick Cookbook, Chapter Two, 1971 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0041)
    Note: Spokesperson Betty Crocker
  - Two In The Kitchen: Betty Crocker's Bisquick Cookbook, Supplement One, 1972 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0042)
    Note: Spokesperson Betty Crocker with coupon on inside back cover
  - Vanilla Desserts Cookbook, 1972 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0043)
    Company: Lewis, Neale Inc.
    Product: 100% Real Vanilla
    Note: has original envelope
  - All Time Baking Soda Favorites Treasured Recipes Modernized for Easy Baking, circa 1970s (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0044)
    Note: with original envelope
  - The Calumet Treasury of Home Baking: A Collection of Plain and Fancy Recipes You'll Want to Bake Again and Again, 1971 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0045)
  - All Occasion Beverage Book, circa 1970s (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0046)
    Company: Coca-Cola Company
    Product: Minute Maid frozen concentrates
  - Go Creative with Minute Maid, 1971 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0047)
  - Happy Holiday Helper from Sanka, 1979 (Box 1970s-01, Item 1970s-0048)
    Product: Sanka coffee products
    Note: Holiday Guide – no recipes